{"data":[{"question":"The ode was original a ceremonial poem written to celebrate public occasions or exalted subjects.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"original","b":"a ceremonial","c":"written to","d":"or","answer":"1","explain":"- Original-> originally","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Knowledge of the rate at which a ship is traveling through the water is important if the navigator need to estimate the time of arrival.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Knowledge of","b":"at which","c":"through","d":"need to ","answer":"4","explain":"- Need-> needs","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The earth is the only planet with a large number of oxygen in its atmosphere.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the","b":"number","c":"oxygen","d":"its","answer":"2","explain":"- Number-> amount","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A painter who lived most of his life in the Middle West, Grant wood has called America's Painter of the Soil.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"most","b":"his life","c":"has called","d":"Painter of the Soil","answer":"3","explain":"- Has called-> has been called","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"While ancient times people simply painted inanimate objects, during the Renaissance the painting of  still life developed as an accepted art form.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"While ancient","b":"during","c":"of","d":"developed as","answer":"1","explain":"- While->in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The American frontiersman, politician, and soldier Davy crockett is one of the most  popular of American hero.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"frontiersman","b":"most","c":"of","d":"hero","answer":"4","explain":"- Hero-> heroes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Three months after they have been laid, crocodile eggs are ready hatched.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"laid","b":"crocodile ","c":"ready ","d":"hatched","answer":"4","explain":"- Hatched-> to be harched","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Peas require rich soil, constant moistures, and a cool growing season to develop well.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"rich ","b":"moistures","c":"growing ","d":"well","answer":"2","explain":"- Moistures-> moisture","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A dolphin locates underwater objects in its path by doing a series of clicking and whistling sounds.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in ","b":"its ","c":"doing ","d":"whistling ","answer":"4","explain":"- Whistling-> Whistle","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A desert area that has been without water for six years will still bloom when rain will come.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has been ","b":"without water ","c":"still ","d":"will come","answer":"4","explain":"- Will rain-> rains","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}